{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": " Where did Adam and Eve live? (Genesis 2:8)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " Eden "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Sodom "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Zion "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Israel "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " Eden ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " Which two trees grew in the midst of the garden? (Genesis 2:9)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " The tree of death and the tree of joy and despair "
        },
        {
          "choice": " The tree of life and the tree of death "
        },
        {
          "choice": " The tree of knowledge of good and evil and the tree of joy and despair "
        },
        {
          "choice": " The tree of life and the tree of knowledge of good and evil "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " The tree of life and the tree of knowledge of good and evil ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " Which tree bore fruit that God forbade Adam and Eve to partake of ? (Genesis 2:16-17)  ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " The tree of life "
        },
        {
          "choice": " The tree of death "
        },
        {
          "choice": " The tree of knowledge of good and evil "
        },
        {
          "choice": " The tree of joy and despair "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " The tree of knowledge of good and evil ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " What would NOT happen to anyone who would partake of such fruit?  (Genesis 3:16-19)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " They would become all-knowing "
        },
        {
          "choice": " They would know for themselves the difference between right and wrong "
        },
        {
          "choice": " They would be able to bear children "
        },
        {
          "choice": " They would die "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " They would become all-knowing ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " What animal deceived Eve? (Genesis 3:1-6)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " A wolf "
        },
        {
          "choice": " A fox "
        },
        {
          "choice": " A crow "
        },
        {
          "choice": " A serpent "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " A serpent ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " The animal who deceived Eve represents: (Genesis 1:20-23)",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " Adam "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Jesus "
        },
        {
          "choice": " The spirits of Eve's unborn children "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Lucifer "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " Jesus ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " What did the deceptive animal convince Eve to do? (Genesis 3:1-6) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " Partake of the forbidden fruit "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Kill an animal "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Leave Adam "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Blaspheme against the Lord "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " Partake of the forbidden fruit ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " What did Adam do after Eve obeyed the animal and transgressed against the Lord's commandment? (Genesis 3:6) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " He forgave her "
        },
        {
          "choice": " He condemned her "
        },
        {
          "choice": " He exiled her "
        },
        {
          "choice": " He also transgressed against the Lord's commandment "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " He also transgressed against the Lord's commandment ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " Why did Adam hide himself from the Lord? (Genesis 3:10) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " He was embarrassed because he realized he was naked "
        },
        {
          "choice": " He wanted to see if he could outwit the Lord "
        },
        {
          "choice": " He wanted the Lord to prove to him that He can see all"
        },
        {
          "choice": " He was ashamed of his wife's transgression "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " He was embarrassed because he realized he was naked ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    },
    {
      "question": " What did the Lord NOT do as a result of the disobedience of Adam and Eve? (Genesis 3:16-19) ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " Give them the ability to feel emotion "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Cause them to work the ground for food "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Cast them out of Eden and His presence "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Kill them instantly "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " Kill them instantly ",
      "type": "epi_1"
    }
  ]
}